Alexi Daniel Saravia

New Iberia, LA 70560 · linkedin.com/in/iodaniels · +1 (337) 492 8394 · danviaz@gmail.com

More than 7 years of experience as a Software Engineer. Developing digital products for the health, logistics and retail industry, with +10 thousand users on a recurring basis monthly, generating +50 thousand transactions monthly between all the digital products developed.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Multisoft Honduras

San Pedro Sula, Honduras

March 2022-November 2024

- Mid-Senior Software Engineer

 Led a team in developing and
 - Led a team in developing and maintaining web applications using JavaScript, React.js, Python and Django. Implemented RESTful APIs and integrated with Postgresql databases. Collaborated with stakeholders to define project requirements and timelines.
 - Developing and maintaining web platform for business sales management in the health industry, managing +3 thousand work orders monthly, optimizing the critical processes involved in the business sales division, increasing sales by 10% monthly.
 - Developing and maintaining web application to make quotes for clinical studies, processing +5 thousand quotes monthly.

San Pedro Sula, Honduras

October 2020-March 2022

Full-stack Engineer

• Developed and maintained web applications using JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, Python and Django. Designed and implemented RESTful APIs for data communication. Collaborated with crossfunctional teams to deliver high-quality software products on schedule.

San Pedro Sula, Honduras

Junior Software Engineer

May 2018 - October 2019

• Contributed to the development of web applications using JavaScript, React, Python and Django. Managed databases and implemented data storage solutions using MySQL and MongoDB. Worked closely with product managers to prioritize features and enhancements.

EDUCATION

Autonomous University of Honduras in the Sula Valley

San Pedro Sula, Honduras

Computer Systems Engineering

Aug 2023

SKILLS

• Languages: Spanish (native), English